

Marjon G. Castillano

Address: Blk. 8 Lot 36 C1, Deca Homes Baywalk Phase, Brgy. Dumlog Talisay City, Cebu

6045

Contact No: (032) 2558141/+63 926-039-1562

Email: esapirian@gmail.com

ServiceNow/ Application Developer – Web Technologies with 4 years of experience in front-end development.

Skilled in developing UI using ReactJS, CSS, HTML and Javascript.

A Certified System Administrator - ServiceNow

Have an excellent interpersonal skills.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Front-end Developer
- ServiceNow Developer
- Scrum Master
- System Administrator
- Security Administrator

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Accenture Inc. Cebu City, Cebu Philippines

Servicenow Developer – September 2022 to present ServiceNow Certified System Administrator

• Develop the UI side and backend side of the application using servicenow

IBM Solutions Delivery Inc., Cebu City, Cebu Philippines

Application Developer – ReactJS, CSS, HTML and Javascript // May 2017 – September 2022

- Develop the UI side of the application using React JS
- Fixed some bugs that I encountered and documented the solutions.
- · Developed new features for our application.
- · Webscraping using Mozenda tool.

Scrum Master // January 2019 – September 2022

- Leading the sprint planning.
- · Doing the daily scrum meetings.
- Assigning tasks to my colleagues.

System Administrator // February 2015 – April 2017

- Provisioned, upgraded and decommissioned servers with different OS types(AIX, Linux and Windows)
- Fixed issues of the servers in a timely-manner.
- Respond quickly to client's tickets by updating/replying to it. Explain the problem and create the solutions for the problem.
- Applied patches to all my assigned servers if ever there will be updates.
- Maintained the servers by solving also the vulnerabilities that may cause the servers not secured.
- Supported also one of the middlewares in IBM, which is WAS(Websphere Application Server).
- Collaborated with my colleagues for our team tasks and reports.

Security Administrator // March 2012 – January 2015

- Team Lead (MAD Mixed Address Databases).
- Register, update and remove servers in MAD record.
- Helped in applying patches to the servers.
- Helped in fixing vulnerabilities of the servers
- Solved tickets in a timely-manner.
- Collaborated and Managed my team members.

EDUCATION

Cebu Institute of Technology-University, Cebu City, Cebu Philippines

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, March 2012

- Cum Laude
- One of the officers to these organizations:
 - Honor's Society
 - DOST sa CIT-U
 - Computer Students' Society

SKILLS

- Application Developer Web Technologies – CSS, HTML, Javascript, React JS
- ServiceNow Development
- Security Administration
- AIX, Linux and Windows Administration
- Middleware: DB2

Badges Earned in IBM

- IBM Mentor
- IBM Agile Explorer
- Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner
- Blockchain Essentials for Developers
- Big Data Foundaitons Level 1
- Data Science Foundaitons –

Level 1

Hadoop Foundations – Level 1

AWARDS in IBM

- Bayani Award 2013 Group Award from the client
- Top Talent 2015 Having a high performance rate for the past 3 consecutive performance rating.
- Top Talent 2016 Having a high performance rate for the past 3 consecutive performance rating.
- WPS(Work Place Security) Inspector January 2014 to present
 - to make sure that the workplace is compliance to secure clients and personal data.
- IBM Club Director -(For Cebu Events) January 2015 to December 2017
 - leads all IBM activities for people's engagement.
 - organizes events for the company.

CHARACTER REFERENCES

Chari Flor T. Supino SAP/ABAP Developer Accenture IT Park Lahug, Cebu City Contact #: +63999-224-2700 Allen C. Montejo Project Manager/PeM IBM 7th Flr. 2Quad Bldg, Cardinal Rosales Ave., Cebu Business Park Contact #: +63915-706-2465